{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814942671","data":{"timestamp":" 947814942671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814943634","data":{"timestamp":" 947814943634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814946598","data":{"timestamp":" 947814946598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814947130","data":{"timestamp":" 947814947130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814947773","data":{"timestamp":" 947814947773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814951900","data":{"timestamp":" 947814951900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814952823","data":{"timestamp":" 947814952823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814956454","data":{"timestamp":" 947814956454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814957237","data":{"timestamp":" 947814957237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814958210","data":{"timestamp":" 947814958210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814962119","data":{"timestamp":" 947814962119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814963083","data":{"timestamp":" 947814963083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814966010","data":{"timestamp":" 947814966010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814966543","data":{"timestamp":" 947814966543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814967187","data":{"timestamp":" 947814967187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814971306","data":{"timestamp":" 947814971306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814972229","data":{"timestamp":" 947814972229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814975854","data":{"timestamp":" 947814975854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814976637","data":{"timestamp":" 947814976637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814977610","data":{"timestamp":" 947814977610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814980919","data":{"timestamp":" 947814980919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947814980970","data":{"timestamp":" 947814980970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 061ff4a6-6375-4561-9a7b-7c77cb434498"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815000345","data":{"timestamp":" 947815000345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 22c21424-cc38-4bea-be6f-c0098dee210f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815009789","data":{"timestamp":" 947815009789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 22c21424-cc38-4bea-be6f-c0098dee210f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815016935","data":{"timestamp":" 947815016935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 22c21424-cc38-4bea-be6f-c0098dee210f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815025771","data":{"timestamp":" 947815025771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 22c21424-cc38-4bea-be6f-c0098dee210f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815033195","data":{"timestamp":" 947815033195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 22c21424-cc38-4bea-be6f-c0098dee210f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815050113","data":{"timestamp":" 947815050113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815066158","data":{"timestamp":" 947815066157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815067742","data":{"timestamp":" 947815067742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815070814","data":{"timestamp":" 947815070813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815072428","data":{"timestamp":" 947815072427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815075326","data":{"timestamp":" 947815075325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815076961","data":{"timestamp":" 947815076960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815085549","data":{"timestamp":" 947815085548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" START_AKALALA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815090486","data":{"timestamp":" 947815090485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" START_AKALALA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815096143","data":{"timestamp":" 947815096141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815097760","data":{"timestamp":" 947815097759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815105281","data":{"timestamp":" 947815105280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" START_ANACHEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815107432","data":{"timestamp":" 947815107432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815109065","data":{"timestamp":" 947815109064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815123391","data":{"timestamp":" 947815123390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815124992","data":{"timestamp":" 947815124992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815128061","data":{"timestamp":" 947815128061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" START_ANGANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815130368","data":{"timestamp":" 947815130367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815131935","data":{"timestamp":" 947815131935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815134707","data":{"timestamp":" 947815134707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815136316","data":{"timestamp":" 947815136315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815169288","data":{"timestamp":" 947815169288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815170900","data":{"timestamp":" 947815170899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815178983","data":{"timestamp":" 947815178983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815180621","data":{"timestamp":" 947815180620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815183181","data":{"timestamp":" 947815183181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815185201","data":{"timestamp":" 947815185200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815185301","data":{"timestamp":" 947815185300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b621fe1b-ce01-4b2e-8c30-33dff0467ab9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815196736","data":{"timestamp":" 947815196735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815196965","data":{"timestamp":" 947815196965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815197939","data":{"timestamp":" 947815197938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815199212","data":{"timestamp":" 947815199212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815202115","data":{"timestamp":" 947815202115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815202958","data":{"timestamp":" 947815202958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815203272","data":{"timestamp":" 947815203271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815204504","data":{"timestamp":" 947815204504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815208069","data":{"timestamp":" 947815208068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815209060","data":{"timestamp":" 947815209060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815209319","data":{"timestamp":" 947815209319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815210275","data":{"timestamp":" 947815210274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815213151","data":{"timestamp":" 947815213151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815214193","data":{"timestamp":" 947815214193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815214676","data":{"timestamp":" 947815214676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815219267","data":{"timestamp":" 947815219266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815219374","data":{"timestamp":" 947815219374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4c0e5db6-3078-47cb-b0b2-95373611c1cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815236041","data":{"timestamp":" 947815236041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6f3e88e9-d727-423a-bf37-45c16ef5328c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nchi-ng'i-mbi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815247825","data":{"timestamp":" 947815247825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6f3e88e9-d727-423a-bf37-45c16ef5328c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mchi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815253532","data":{"timestamp":" 947815253532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6f3e88e9-d727-423a-bf37-45c16ef5328c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815254617","data":{"timestamp":" 947815254617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6f3e88e9-d727-423a-bf37-45c16ef5328c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815271702","data":{"timestamp":" 947815271701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815280012","data":{"timestamp":" 947815280011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815289406","data":{"timestamp":" 947815289406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815302566","data":{"timestamp":" 947815302566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815314544","data":{"timestamp":" 947815314544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815326339","data":{"timestamp":" 947815326339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815340109","data":{"timestamp":" 947815340109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815340607","data":{"timestamp":" 947815340607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815346439","data":{"timestamp":" 947815346439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815360850","data":{"timestamp":" 947815360850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815370197","data":{"timestamp":" 947815370197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815380711","data":{"timestamp":" 947815380711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815390448","data":{"timestamp":" 947815390448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815402973","data":{"timestamp":" 947815402973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815413349","data":{"timestamp":" 947815413349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815422162","data":{"timestamp":" 947815422161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 55c2df6f-0b98-4d3c-bdd6-8a7093749931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815432510","data":{"timestamp":" 947815432510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_li-mbi-fi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815436794","data":{"timestamp":" 947815436794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mchi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815445609","data":{"timestamp":" 947815445608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815452314","data":{"timestamp":" 947815452314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ndi-nchi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815458202","data":{"timestamp":" 947815458202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nyi-mbi-wi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815462654","data":{"timestamp":" 947815462654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nchi-ng'i-mbi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815468867","data":{"timestamp":" 947815468867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-fi-vyi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815474195","data":{"timestamp":" 947815474195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ji-hi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815478797","data":{"timestamp":" 947815478797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nji-ri-mbi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815483232","data":{"timestamp":" 947815483232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_ng'i-shi-mbi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815487925","data":{"timestamp":" 947815487925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_twi-mbi-ni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815493679","data":{"timestamp":" 947815493678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" d960042f-6589-4a76-a11d-488ea05869f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_twi-mbi-ni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815508766","data":{"timestamp":" 947815508766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_ng'i-shi-mbi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815512688","data":{"timestamp":" 947815512688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ji-hi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815516786","data":{"timestamp":" 947815516786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815520908","data":{"timestamp":" 947815520908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nyi-mbi-wi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" wi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815526281","data":{"timestamp":" 947815526281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nyi-mbi-wi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815531822","data":{"timestamp":" 947815531822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ndi-nchi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815536037","data":{"timestamp":" 947815536037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nchi-ng'i-mbi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" nchi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815541918","data":{"timestamp":" 947815541918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nchi-ng'i-mbi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815546142","data":{"timestamp":" 947815546142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_li-mbi-fi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815552306","data":{"timestamp":" 947815552306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_li-mbi-fi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815557440","data":{"timestamp":" 947815557439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-fi-vyi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815562072","data":{"timestamp":" 947815562072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nji-ri-mbi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815566385","data":{"timestamp":" 947815566385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_twi-mbi-ni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" twi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815572684","data":{"timestamp":" 947815572683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_twi-mbi-ni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815578411","data":{"timestamp":" 947815578410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 0d0c9a8e-0bc8-4ada-826e-c5c0e32c167e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_twi-mbi-ni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815593503","data":{"timestamp":" 947815593503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_twi-mbi-ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815608850","data":{"timestamp":" 947815608850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nji-ri-mbi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815616414","data":{"timestamp":" 947815616413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ndi-nchi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" ndi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815622197","data":{"timestamp":" 947815622196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ndi-nchi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815626596","data":{"timestamp":" 947815626596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nchi-ng'i-mbi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815630804","data":{"timestamp":" 947815630804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815634896","data":{"timestamp":" 947815634896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ji-hi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815639813","data":{"timestamp":" 947815639813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_li-mbi-fi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815644105","data":{"timestamp":" 947815644105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_ng'i-shi-mbi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815649057","data":{"timestamp":" 947815649057"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-fi-vyi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815653982","data":{"timestamp":" 947815653982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nyi-mbi-wi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815659757","data":{"timestamp":" 947815659756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" dcfe7e02-4b14-4ff2-ae85-6c6968205df3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nyi-mbi-wi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815668786","data":{"timestamp":" 947815668786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815669014","data":{"timestamp":" 947815669014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815669988","data":{"timestamp":" 947815669988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815671262","data":{"timestamp":" 947815671262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815674154","data":{"timestamp":" 947815674154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815675005","data":{"timestamp":" 947815675005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815675323","data":{"timestamp":" 947815675323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815676573","data":{"timestamp":" 947815676572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815680133","data":{"timestamp":" 947815680133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815681120","data":{"timestamp":" 947815681120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815681378","data":{"timestamp":" 947815681378"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815682331","data":{"timestamp":" 947815682331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815685257","data":{"timestamp":" 947815685255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815686295","data":{"timestamp":" 947815686295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815686783","data":{"timestamp":" 947815686783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815691360","data":{"timestamp":" 947815691358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815691519","data":{"timestamp":" 947815691519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 6d0797a6-d2a9-41fa-bcbd-51f318dd6137"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815704660","data":{"timestamp":" 947815704660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mza_mwi-mza-mgu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mza"," userResponse":" mza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815719170","data":{"timestamp":" 947815719170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nje"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815723503","data":{"timestamp":" 947815723502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_she-vya-nge"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815728194","data":{"timestamp":" 947815728194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mna-mle-kwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815733135","data":{"timestamp":" 947815733135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815737970","data":{"timestamp":" 947815737969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mwu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815749430","data":{"timestamp":" 947815749430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815757747","data":{"timestamp":" 947815757747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" nju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815763340","data":{"timestamp":" 947815763339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815774694","data":{"timestamp":" 947815774694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815779070","data":{"timestamp":" 947815779070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mfa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815784792","data":{"timestamp":" 947815784792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" b6978f3c-2455-478d-9b36-4c3cb0e30316"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815800393","data":{"timestamp":" 947815800393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 8cccec7d-9cda-42bb-8dbe-764faf60237b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815808948","data":{"timestamp":" 947815808948"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 8cccec7d-9cda-42bb-8dbe-764faf60237b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815814243","data":{"timestamp":" 947815814243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 8cccec7d-9cda-42bb-8dbe-764faf60237b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815817395","data":{"timestamp":" 947815817395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 8cccec7d-9cda-42bb-8dbe-764faf60237b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815827913","data":{"timestamp":" 947815827913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 8cccec7d-9cda-42bb-8dbe-764faf60237b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815832894","data":{"timestamp":" 947815832894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 8cccec7d-9cda-42bb-8dbe-764faf60237b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815853616","data":{"timestamp":" 947815853616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_bwa_cho_chu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815860241","data":{"timestamp":" 947815860241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_gha_chi_mli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815866908","data":{"timestamp":" 947815866908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vya_mdo_che"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815873512","data":{"timestamp":" 947815873512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mti_mji_mno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815880954","data":{"timestamp":" 947815880953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mti_mji_mno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815891494","data":{"timestamp":" 947815891494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mti_mji_mno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815898116","data":{"timestamp":" 947815898116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mlu_mbi_mli"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815904738","data":{"timestamp":" 947815904737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ngi_shi_kwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815911377","data":{"timestamp":" 947815911377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vyi_nji_kwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815918851","data":{"timestamp":" 947815918850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vyi_nji_kwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815925457","data":{"timestamp":" 947815925457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nja_sha_mto"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815932128","data":{"timestamp":" 947815932128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vyu_mki_nju"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815938750","data":{"timestamp":" 947815938750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_chi_ndu_ngu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815951877","data":{"timestamp":" 947815951877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_chi_ndu_ngu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947815958833","data":{"timestamp":" 947815958832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_045524"," gameId":" 4a787d8a-43e4-4daf-b2ac-ba274ba497f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.3ch..3ch.noShow..26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_chi_ndu_ngu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}